{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0010", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Rosedale?", "answer": "171", "type": "how many airbnbs"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0011", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Flatlands?", "answer": "217", "type": "how many airbnbs"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0012", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Brighton Beach?", "answer": "168", "type": "how many airbnbs"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0013", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Whitestone?", "answer": "26", "type": "how many airbnbs"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0014", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Jamaica Estates?", "answer": "50", "type": "how many airbnbs"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0015", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Windsor Terrace?", "answer": "331", "type": "how many airbnbs"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0016", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Port Richmond?", "answer": "25", "type": "how many airbnbs"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0017", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Bronxdale?", "answer": "48", "type": "how many airbnbs"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0018", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Roosevelt Island?", "answer": "159", "type": "how many airbnbs"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0019", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Van Nest?", "answer": "26", "type": "how many airbnbs"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0020", "question": "What is the average price of airbnbs in Boerum Hill?", "answer": "$627.0", "type": "average price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0021", "question": "What is the average price of airbnbs in Schuylerville?", "answer": "$659.4", "type": "average price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0022", "question": "What is the average price of airbnbs in Maspeth?", "answer": "$597.0", "type": "average price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0023", "question": "What is the average price of airbnbs in Sheepshead Bay?", "answer": "$624.9", "type": "average price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0024", "question": "What is the average price of airbnbs in Grant City?", "answer": "$558.2", "type": "average price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0025", "question": "What is the average price of airbnbs in East Morrisania?", "answer": "$764.7", "type": "average price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0026", "question": "What is the average price of airbnbs in Howland Hook?", "answer": "$657.3", "type": "average price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0027", "question": "What is the average price of airbnbs in Glen Oaks?", "answer": "$550.5", "type": "average price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0028", "question": "What is the average price of airbnbs in Queens Village?", "answer": "$661.9", "type": "average price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0029", "question": "What is the average price of airbnbs in Stuyvesant Town?", "answer": "$680.9", "type": "average price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0040", "question": "How much proporion of airbnbs in West Brighton have a flexible cancellation policy?", "answer": "0.3", "type": "proporion of airbnbs"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0041", "question": "How much proporion of airbnbs in Fordham have a flexible cancellation policy?", "answer": "0.3", "type": "proporion of airbnbs"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0042", "question": "How much proporion of airbnbs in Ditmars Steinway have a flexible cancellation policy?", "answer": "0.3", "type": "proporion of airbnbs"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0043", "question": "How much proporion of airbnbs in Co-op City have a flexible cancellation policy?", "answer": "0.2", "type": "proporion of airbnbs"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0044", "question": "How much proporion of airbnbs in SoHo have a flexible cancellation policy?", "answer": "0.3", "type": "proporion of airbnbs"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0045", "question": "How much proporion of airbnbs in Wakefield have a flexible cancellation policy?", "answer": "0.4", "type": "proporion of airbnbs"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0046", "question": "How much proporion of airbnbs in East Elmhurst have a flexible cancellation policy?", "answer": "0.3", "type": "proporion of airbnbs"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0047", "question": "How much proporion of airbnbs in Wakefield have a flexible cancellation policy?", "answer": "0.4", "type": "proporion of airbnbs"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0048", "question": "How much proporion of airbnbs in Howland Hook have a flexible cancellation policy?", "answer": "0.2", "type": "proporion of airbnbs"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0049", "question": "How much proporion of airbnbs in Stuyvesant Town have a flexible cancellation policy?", "answer": "0.3", "type": "proporion of airbnbs"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0050", "question": "How much does it cost per night to stay at the most expensive Entire home/apt in Eastchester?", "answer": "$1152", "type": "cost per night"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0051", "question": "How much does it cost per night to stay at the most expensive Entire home/apt in Throgs Neck?", "answer": "$1182", "type": "cost per night"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0052", "question": "How much does it cost per night to stay at the most expensive Entire home/apt in Kingsbridge?", "answer": "$1067", "type": "cost per night"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0053", "question": "How much does it cost per night to stay at the most expensive Entire home/apt in Emerson Hill?", "answer": "$1158", "type": "cost per night"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0054", "question": "How much does it cost per night to stay at the most expensive Entire home/apt in Williamsbridge?", "answer": "$1184", "type": "cost per night"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0055", "question": "How much does it cost per night to stay at the most expensive Entire home/apt in Edgemere?", "answer": "$964", "type": "cost per night"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0057", "question": "How much does it cost per night to stay at the most expensive Entire home/apt in Howard Beach?", "answer": "$1195", "type": "cost per night"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0058", "question": "How much does it cost per night to stay at the most expensive Entire home/apt in Kew Gardens?", "answer": "$1030", "type": "cost per night"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0059", "question": "How much does it cost per night to stay at the most expensive Entire home/apt in Fort Wadsworth?", "answer": "$1024", "type": "cost per night"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0060", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Little Italy that have a review rate not lower than 4?", "answer": "119", "type": "airbnb with high rate"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0061", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Springfield Gardens that have a review rate not lower than 4?", "answer": "115", "type": "airbnb with high rate"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0062", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Eltingville that have a review rate not lower than 4?", "answer": "6", "type": "airbnb with high rate"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0063", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Belmont that have a review rate not lower than 4?", "answer": "21", "type": "airbnb with high rate"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0064", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Concord that have a review rate not lower than 4?", "answer": "28", "type": "airbnb with high rate"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0065", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Douglaston that have a review rate not lower than 4?", "answer": "10", "type": "airbnb with high rate"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0066", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Prospect-Lefferts Gardens that have a review rate not lower than 4?", "answer": "550", "type": "airbnb with high rate"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0067", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Randall Manor that have a review rate not lower than 4?", "answer": "25", "type": "airbnb with high rate"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0068", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Financial District that have a review rate not lower than 4?", "answer": "714", "type": "airbnb with high rate"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0069", "question": "How many airbnbs are there in Norwood that have a review rate not lower than 4?", "answer": "32", "type": "airbnb with high rate"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0070", "question": "Can you recommend me a hotel room with the lowest price in College Point?", "answer": "Bedroom has views of nyc skyline.", "type": "room with the lowest price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0071", "question": "Can you recommend me a hotel room with the lowest price in SoHo?", "answer": "Two Twin Room", "type": "room with the lowest price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0072", "question": "Can you recommend me a hotel room with the lowest price in Eltingville?", "answer": "“No Place Like Home”\n1st Floor Suburban Apt.", "type": "room with the lowest price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0073", "question": "Can you recommend me a hotel room with the lowest price in Holliswood?", "answer": "ROOM EN NEW YORK, MANHATTAN", "type": "room with the lowest price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0074", "question": "Can you recommend me a hotel room with the lowest price in Concourse?", "answer": "Multicultural House II", "type": "room with the lowest price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0075", "question": "Can you recommend me a hotel room with the lowest price in Silver Lake?", "answer": "New Apartment, Close to Ferry", "type": "room with the lowest price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0076", "question": "Can you recommend me a hotel room with the lowest price in Bull's Head?", "answer": "Newly Renovated Guest Room with Private Bath", "type": "room with the lowest price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0077", "question": "Can you recommend me a hotel room with the lowest price in Westerleigh?", "answer": "Eclectic Private New Apartment  Westerleigh, S.I.", "type": "room with the lowest price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0079", "question": "Can you recommend me a hotel room with the lowest price in Clifton?", "answer": "Home away from Home: Newly Renovated Apartment", "type": "room with the lowest price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0090", "question": "Can you recommend a Shared room with the lowest price within 10 miles radius from -74.06269614778004 longitude and 40.5813729578663 latitude?", "answer": "BK's Finest SHARED ROOM 1 BED AVAILABLE", "type": "shared room with the lowest price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0091", "question": "Can you recommend a Shared room with the lowest price within 10 miles radius from -73.79998226317166 longitude and 40.581286157201006 latitude?", "answer": "BK's Finest SHARED ROOM 1 BED AVAILABLE", "type": "shared room with the lowest price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0092", "question": "Can you recommend a Shared room with the lowest price within 10 miles radius from -73.70247078883878 longitude and 40.58720602526452 latitude?", "answer": "CrashPadsUSA Hotbeds for Airline Crew ONLY", "type": "shared room with the lowest price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0093", "question": "Can you recommend a Shared room with the lowest price within 10 miles radius from -73.83109495286112 longitude and 40.835727665445795 latitude?", "answer": "BK's Finest SHARED ROOM 1 BED AVAILABLE", "type": "shared room with the lowest price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0094", "question": "Can you recommend a Shared room with the lowest price within 10 miles radius from -74.0426082801347 longitude and 40.689902908795524 latitude?", "answer": "BK's Finest SHARED ROOM 1 BED AVAILABLE", "type": "shared room with the lowest price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0095", "question": "Can you recommend a Shared room with the lowest price within 10 miles radius from -73.72509182668071 longitude and 40.79002903608048 latitude?", "answer": "LowerLevel House NYC,Traveler ShortStay BedRoom", "type": "shared room with the lowest price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0096", "question": "Can you recommend a Shared room with the lowest price within 10 miles radius from -73.81552366025818 longitude and 40.89104376829842 latitude?", "answer": "twin bed in sharing room near Grand Central", "type": "shared room with the lowest price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0097", "question": "Can you recommend a Shared room with the lowest price within 10 miles radius from -74.09292883460675 longitude and 40.72347282747828 latitude?", "answer": "BK's Finest SHARED ROOM 1 BED AVAILABLE", "type": "shared room with the lowest price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0098", "question": "Can you recommend a Shared room with the lowest price within 10 miles radius from -73.91523625637042 longitude and 40.867183473498066 latitude?", "answer": "twin bed in sharing room near Grand Central", "type": "shared room with the lowest price"}
{"qid": "hard-airbnb-0099", "question": "Can you recommend a Shared room with the lowest price within 10 miles radius from -73.89471040722765 longitude and 40.60167851935561 latitude?", "answer": "BK's Finest SHARED ROOM 1 BED AVAILABLE", "type": "shared room with the lowest price"}
